const monthsCards = [
  {
    section: {
      english: 'Months of the Year',
      teReo: "Te Au Marama ō te Mata'iti",
      cards: [
        {
          question: 'January',
          answer: 'Tiānuare',
        },
        {
          question: 'February',
          answer: 'Pēperuare',
        },
        {
          question: 'March',
          answer: 'Māti',
        },
        {
          question: 'April',
          answer: 'Āperirā',
        },
        {
          question: 'May',
          answer: 'Mē',
        },
        {
          question: 'June',
          answer: 'Tiūnu',
        },
        {
          question: 'July',
          answer: 'Tiurai',
        },
        {
          question: 'August',
          answer: 'Aukute',
        },
        {
          question: 'September',
          answer: 'Tepetema',
        },
        {
          question: 'October',
          answer: 'Okotopa',
        },
        {
          question: 'November',
          answer: 'Noema',
        },
        {
          question: 'December',
          answer: 'Tītema',
        },
      ],
    },
  },
]

const daysOfWeekCards = [
  {
    section: {
      english: 'Days of the Week',
      teReo: "Au rā o te 'epetoma",
      cards: [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: 'Monday',
          answer: 'Monitē',
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: 'Tuesday',
          answer: "Ru'irua",
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: 'Wednesday',
          answer: "Ru'itoru",
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: 'Thursday',
          answer: 'Paraparau',
        },
        {
          id: 5,
          question: 'Friday',
          answer: 'Varaire',
        },
        {
          id: 6,
          question: 'Saturday',
          answer: "Ma'anākai",
        },
        {
          id: 7,
          question: 'Sunday',
          answer: 'Tāpati',
        },
      ],
    },
  },
]

const bodyPartsCards = [
  {
    section: {
      english: 'Parts of the Body',
      teReo: "Au Mero 'Ō Te Kōpapa",
    },
    cards: [
      {
        question: 'Head',
        answer: 'Katu',
      },
      {
        question: 'Neck',
        answer: 'Kakī',
      },
      {
        question: 'Eye',
        answer: 'Mata',
      },
      {
        question: 'Mouth',
        answer: "Va'a",
      },
    ],
  },
]
// const meetAndGreetCards = [
//   {
//     section: {
//       english: 'Meet and Greet',
//       teReo: "Au Tū 'Ārāvei'anga"
//     },
//     cards:[
//       {
//         engQuestion: 'How are you?',
//         teReoQuestion: "Pē'ea koe?",
//         engAnswer: 'Great!',
//       }
//     ]
//   }
// ]
const flashcardData = {
  months: monthsCards,
  daysOfWeek: daysOfWeekCards,
}

export default flashcardData
